http://www.ivcu.com/about/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Questions?
Join IVCU
FACTS
WHAT DOES Illinois Valley Credit Union
DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
•
Social Security number and payment history
•
Credit history and transaction or loss history
•
Account transactions and checking account information
When you are no longer a credit union member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members personal information; the reasons Illinois Valley Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does
Credit Union Share?
Can You limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
YES
NO
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
For joint marketing with other financial companies
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your transactions and experiences
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
For our affiliates to market to you
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
For nonaffiliates to market to you
NO
WE DON’T SHARE
Questions?
Call (815) 224 -2666 or go to www.ivcu.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
ILLINOIS VALLEY CREDIT UNION
What we do
How does IVCU
protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does IVCU
collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
•
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
•
affiliates from using your information to market to you
•
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
•
Illinois Valley Credit Union has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
•
Illinois Valley Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
